<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- Strings for main activity of app -->
    <string name="app_name">International Studies</string>
    <string name="mainTitle">Center for International Studies and Programs Mobile App</string>
    <string name="mainAdviseTitle">Academic Advising</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="mainAdmissionsTitle">Admissions Information</string>
    <string name="mainExchangeTitle">Exchange Program</string>
    <string name="mainServicesTitle">Student and Faculty services</string>
    <string name="mainOtherTitle">Other Resources</string>
    <string name="mainStudyTitle">Study Abroad</string>
    <string name="mainAboutCispTitle">About Us</string>

    <!-- Strings for Main Activity for Academic Advising -->
    <string name="title_activity_second_advise">International Advising</string>
    <string name="headerAdvise">International Advising</string>
    <string name="adviseParagraph">The primary purpose of the academic
        advising program at California State University San Bernardino
        is to assist students in the development and implementation of
        meaningful educational plans that are compatible with their life
        goals. The program provides opportunities for students to assess
        their interests and academic abilities, encouraging their fullest
        intellectual development. Students at CSUSB will receive
        ongoing support empowering them to accomplish their personal,
        educational, and professional goals.</string>
    <string name="cispButtonTitle">About CISP and Staff</string>
    <string name="informationItemButtonTitle">Informational Items</string>
    <string name="testOrientationButtonTitle">Orientation and Testing</string>

    <!-- Strings for About CISP page -->
    <string name="title_activity_about_cisp">About CISP</string>
    <string name="aboutCispHeader">About Us</string>
    <string name="aboutCispDescrip">The Center for International Studies (CISP) supports
        international students who come to study at CSUSB as permanent students or as part of
        exchange programs. We also offer support to CSUSB students who wish to study abroad.\n\n
        CISP offers help with advising, course selection and registration, fee and tuition payment,
        housing, scholarships and other aspects of academic life necessary for success at CSUSB.\n\n</string>
    <string name="organizationalChartButtonTitle">CISP Organizational Chart</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cisp_organizational_chart">CISP Organizational Chart</string>

    <!-- String for CISP Staff Page -->
    <string name="cispStaff">CISP Staff</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cisp_staff">CISP Staff</string>
    <string name="cispStaffBody">     Paul Amaya\n
     Director, CISP\n
     pamaya@csusb.edu\n
     (909) 537-5193\n\n

     Dr.Rueyling Chuang\n
     Faculty Director, CISP\n
     rchuang@csusb.edu\n
     (909) 537-9537\n\n

     Wen-Yang James Cheng\n
     Information Technology Consultant\n
     wcheng@csusb.edu\n
     (909) 537-5193\n \n

     Cynthia Shum\n
     Assistant Director/International Admissions\n
     cshum@csusb.edu\n
     (909) 537-5212\n\n

     Nancy Lopez\n
     International Admissions Counselor\n
     nlopez@csusb.edu\n
     (909) 537-5204\n\n

     Mika Ozaki-Gonzalez\n
     International Application Processor\n
     mozaki@csusb.edu\n
     (909) 537-5284\n\n

     Nancy Fu\n
     International Academic Program Officer\n
     nancyf@csusb.edu\n
     (909) 537-7480\n\n

     Elanor Perry\n
     Immigration Specialist\n
     eperry@csusb.edu\n
     (909) 537-3195\n\n

     Marco Lagos\n
     SEVIS Coordinator\n
     mlagos@csusb.edu\n
     (909) 537-5193\n\n

     Rika Dawson\n
     Administrative Assistant\n
     rdawson@csusb.edu\n
     (909) 537-5193\n\n

     Aida Cadavid\n
     Program Assistant\n
     aida@csusb.edu\n
     (909) 537-5197\n\n

     Elva Salgado\n
     Study Aborad Coordinator\n
     esalgado@csusb.edu\n
     (909) 537-3204\n\n

     Ankita Thapliyal-Peoples\n
     International Communications &amp; Social Media Specialist\n
     ankita@csusb.edu\n
     (909) 537-3762\n\n

     Adrian Alvarez\n
     International Admissions Evaluator/Graphic Design\n
     aalvarez@csusb.edu\n
     (909) 537-3269\n</string>

    <!-- Strings for Other Resources Page -->

    <string name="title_activity_other_resources">Other Resources</string>
    <string name="otherResourcesHeader">Other Resources</string>
    <string name="healthInsuranceButtonTitle">Health Insurance</string>
    <string name="campusMapButtonTitle">Campus Map</string>
    <string name="housingButtonTitle">Housing</string>

    <!-- Strings for Health Insurance Page -->
    <string name="title_activity_health_insurance">Health Insurance</string>
    <string name="healthInsuranceHeader">Health Insurance Requirements</string>
    <string name="f1StudentDescrip"><u>F-1 Student</u>\n\n
        Insurance is a requirement. Effective Aug. 1, 1995, all F-1 and J-1 visa applicants must
        agree to obtain and maintain health insurance as a condition of registration and continued
        enrollment in the California State University. This is a condition of receiving an I-20 or
        DS-2019 form. Such insurance must be in amounts as specified by the United States
        Information Agency (USIA) and NAFSA: Association of International Educators. The campus
        president or designee shall determine which insurance policies meet these criteria. Further
        information may be obtained from the Center for International Studies and Programs.</string>
    <string name="j1StudentDescrip"><u>J-1 Student/Scholar</u>\n\n
        The U.S. Information Agency requires all J-1 Exchange Visitors and their accompanying
        dependents to have health and accident insurance at the following minimum level of
        coverage:\n\n
            \t•medical benefits of at least $50,000 per accident or illness\n
            \t•repatriation of remains in the amount of $7,500\n
            \t•expenses associated with medical evacuation in the amount of $10,000\n
            \t•deductible not to exceed $500 per accident/illness\n\n
        Therefore, J-1 scholars are required to either purchase sufficient health insurance in
        their country, or upon arrival in the US may purchase health insurance which meets the
        minimum requirements.<b>In other words, if you don’t have the required health insurance
        from another provider, you must purchase it through the Center for International Studies
        and Programs.</b>\n
        If health insurance coverage is purchased from another source, the insurance corporation
        underwriting the policy must have one of the following ratings:\n\n
        \t•an A.M. Best rating of “A-” or above\n
        \t•an Insurance Solvency International, Ltd., (ISI) rating of “A-i” or above\n
        \t•a Standard &amp; Poor’s Claims paying Ability rating of “A-” or above\n
        \t•a Weiss Research, Inc. rating of “B+” or above\n
        \t•insurance coverage backed by the full faith and credit of your home government\n\n
        meets these requirements.\n\n <b>The U.S. government regulations require the University to notify the U.S. Information
            Agency and to terminate my J-1 exchange visitor status if they determine that you have
            willfully failed to comply with the insurance requirements.</b></string>
    <string name="title_activity_campus_map">campusMap</string>
    <string name="title_activity_housing">housing</string>

    <!-- Strings for Housing Page -->
    <string name="housingHeader">Housing</string>
    <string name="onCampusHousingHeader"><b><u>On Campus Housing</u></b></string>
    <string name="onCampusDescrip">        There is also housing available on campus for exchange visitors but availability is very
        limited. You can e-mail conference@csusb.edu. Please refer your e-mail to Ruth Landeros
        and she will be able to assist you in finding housing on campus, if it is available. DO
        NOT try to get on campus housing through the link directly below because that
        is only for students and they require a Coyote One ID#.!!</string>
    <string name="onCampusForStudentsButtonTitle">On Campus Housing for Students</string>
    <string name="title_activity_housing_on_campus_web_site">housingOnCampusWebSite</string>
    <string name="offCampusHeader"><b><u>Off Campus Housing</u></b></string>
    <string name="offCampusDescrip">WHAT YOU NEED TO KNOW BEFORE RENTING AN APARTMENT\n\n

        It is very difficult to find short-term, furnished housing options in the US. Therefore,
        you are advised to live in university residence halls when possible. Living in a residence
        hall provides the convenience of a furnished room and a meal plan. In addition, you're
        close to university classrooms, libraries and college life. However it is very difficult
        to get a room on campus because the dorms do fill up quickly. Below are some options of
        Apartments around CSU, San Bernardino.</string>


</resources>
